# HIMANSHU AGRAWAL

 $+91~8625952366 \diamond$  Amravati, Maharashtra

\$\$ himanshuag 8625@gmail.com \$\$ linked in.com/in/himanshu-agrawal-1011 \$\$ https://aghimanshu.github.io/Resume-Portfoliongly for the complex of the com

### **OBJECTIVE**

Program Analyst and Full Stack .NET Developer specializing in .NET Core MVC, C, Ajax, Admin LTE, JavaScript, and jQuery. Nearly 3 years of experience in web application development and user support. Seeking roles in innovative projects.

### **EDUCATION**

Master of Computer Application, Nagpur University	2019 - 2021
Bachelor of Computer Application, Amravati University	2016 - 2019

### **SKILLS**

Technical Skills
Applications
Soft Skills

.Net Core, .Net, C, LINQ, Dot Net MVC, SQL Server, Angular JS, Javascript, JQuery, Ajax Visual Studio, Sql Server, Github, Power BI, Label Studio, Jira, NetBeans, Slack, Teams Problem-solving, Analytical Thinking, Teamwork, Communication, Patience

# **EXPERIENCE**

# Program Analyst WNS Global Services

Dec 2022 - Current Nashik. Maharashtra

• Spearheaded global MVC web application development at Eculine, enhancing user experience and worldwide shipment tracking.

- Crafted beginner-level VBA macros for Power BI Label Studio at Potrix.
- Designed dynamic dashboards utilizing Admin LTE and Excel datasets for impactful data visualization with Power BI.

### Software Developer

Aug 2021 - Dec 2022

GIF Technologies

Nagpur, Maharashtra

- Spearheaded development of a centralized dashboard with a feature-subfeature system, enhancing accessibility across multiple campuses.
- Designed and implemented a secure student document module using SHA-256 encryption for seamless cross-campus access.
- Developed a GICC Fees Module to streamline monthly student fee collection and membership management for cultural events.

### Software Developer Intern

Cyberathon

Feb 2021 - Aug 2021

 $Nagpur,\ Maharashtra$ 

• Specialize in MVC development, overseeing product development for an ERP Catering Management System. Expertise in modules for Food Service, Kitchen operations, and Service management. Completed an internship focusing on MVC-based development of a Catering Management System, specializing in Service, Kitchen, and Admin modules.

#### **PROJECTS**

Adhar Authentication for Government Schemes. Developed Aadhar Authentication and Clearance Management systems for government schemes during MCA studies.

**Tour Guide Management** Created a Tour Guide application for Amravati city, enhancing exploration of nearby attractions and lodging options during BCA projects.

# **EXTRA-CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES**

- Outstanding Performer Award from WNS.
- The Annual Cultural extravaganza 'Pratishruti 2020.
- Stand-Out Performer At GIF.
- Leading student clubs or organizations.
- Participating in sports or artistic endeavors.
- The Annual college magazine Arceon'20.
- Participated and Win prinze in Blind-Coding, Error Debugging and Building Logic competitions.
- Participated in debate competitions.
- Leading student clubs or organizations.
- Participating in sports or artistic endeavors.